[
  {
    "question": "I am one in China, two in Indonesia, three in the Philippines, none in Japan. What am I?",
    "answer": "The letter i",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Airplane",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Cars",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "I live on land but in a tree. What am I",
    "answer": "A bird",
    "wrongAnswe1": "A monkey",
    "wrongAnswer2": "An insect",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Nothing"
  },

  {
    "question": "I have three eyes but cannot see. What am I?",
    "answer": "Traffic light",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A ghost",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Tuatara",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "Two handsome racers are having a race. One keeps lapping the other and the race never ends. What am I?",
    "answer": "A clock",
    "wrongAnswer1": "White horse",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Black horse",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Sun and Earth"
  },

  {
    "question": "I jump when I walk and sit when I stand. What am I?",
    "answer": "A kangaroo",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A dog",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A tiger",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A frog"
  },

  {
    "question": "I am an insect. Half of my name is another insect. What am I?",
    "answer": "Beetle",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Housefly",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Grasshopper",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Mosquito"
  },

  {
    "question": "How many bricks does it take to finish a brick building?",
    "answer": "1",
    "wrongAnswer1": "10",
    "wrongAnswer2": "100",
    "wrongAnswer3": "1000"
  },

  {
    "question": "I’m rarely touched but often held and if you’re wise you’ll use me well. What am I?",
    "answer": "Tongue",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Money",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Love",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Advice"
  },

  {
    "question": "I can't go right, i can't go left. I'm forever stuck going only up and down. What am I?",
    "answer": "An elevator",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A clock",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A bouncing ball",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A timer"
  },

  {
    "question": "When I point up, it’s bright. When I point down, it’s dark. What am I?",
    "answer": "A light switch",
    "wrongAnswer1": "The sun",
    "wrongAnswer2": "The moon",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Torchlight"
  },

  {
    "question": "I wave my hands at you, But I never say goodbye. You’re always cool with me, Even cooler when I’m high. What am I?",
    "answer": "An electric fan",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A cassava leaf",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A palm",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "A necessity to some, a treasure to many, I’m best enjoyed among pleasant company. Some like me hot, some like me cold. Some prefer mild, some like me bold.",
    "answer": "Coffee",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Tea",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Pap",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Noodles"
  },

  {
    "question": "I have been hot my entire life. Put me in water or in a freezer for days and I will still be hot. My red color should tell you but don’t be deceived, even when I’m green, I’m still hot. What am I?",
    "answer": "Pepper",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Hot water",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Fire",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Electric iron"
  },

  {
    "question": "I am a rare case where today comes before yesterday. What am I?",
    "answer": "A dictionary",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A leap year",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Last year",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "What breaks on the water but never on land?",
    "answer": "A wave",
    "wrongAnswer1": "An ice",
    "wrongAnswer2": "An egg",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A boat"
  },

  {
    "question": "There are 125 sheep and 5 dogs in a flock. How old is the shepherd?",
    "answer": "No answer",
    "wrongAnswer1": "130",
    "wrongAnswer2": "120",
    "wrongAnswer3": "125"
  },

  {
    "question": "What’s nowhere but everywhere except where something is?",
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Everything",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Something",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "What goes in the water red and comes out black?",
    "answer": "Iron",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Fire",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Firewood",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Nothing"
  },

  {
    "question": "I make you see the beauty of nature through colors, My name makes things weigh less and I have no weight at all. What am I?",
    "answer": "Light",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Fire",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Rainbow",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Phone"
  },

  {
    "question": "Moving to and fro, Dancing all the time. Only to be moved by others to allow them to pass by.",
    "answer": "A door",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Masquerade",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A dancer",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A clown"
  },

  {
    "question": "You can swallow me, but I can swallow you. What am I?",
    "answer": "Water",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Ice",
    "wrongAnswer2": "No answer",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Meat"
  },

  {
    "question": "What asks but never answers?",
    "answer": "A owl",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A chicken",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A dog",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A teacher"
  },

  {
    "question": "My first three letters stores things. Not many people understand me. What am I?",
    "answer": "Binary",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Puzzles",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Riddles",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Trashcan"
  },

  {
    "question": "If you lose me, others around you may lose me too. What am I?",
    "answer": "Temper",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Money",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Truth",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Life"
  },

  {
    "question": "I grow in trees, eat living things but have no teeth and give birth to something that looks nothing like me. What am I?",
    "answer": "A bird",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A snake",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Lizard",
    "wrongAnswer3": "An insect"
  },

  {
    "question": "I have three letters. Cut one off and I become stronger. Cut two off and I become ten. What am I?",
    "answer": "Fox",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Two",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Pot",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "I have two hands but I cannot clap. What am I?",
    "answer": "A clock",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Chicken",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Kangaroo",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A dead man"
  },

  {
    "question": "Anyone can take it as long as it’s on someone.",
    "answer": "Pity",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Money",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Blame",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Nothing"
  },

  {
    "question": "I’m something you might eat, but I also kill. Small children play with me and parents don’t mind. What am I",
    "answer": "Snow",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Chicken",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Cheese",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Pizza"
  },

  {
    "question": "What has feet but no legs?",
    "answer": "A snail",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A duck",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A caterpillar",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A snake"
  },

  {
    "question": "I used to be the light of your life, i’d keep you warm while I cried, now I’m forgotten and tossed away. What am I?",
    "answer": "A candle",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Charcoal",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Matches",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A bulb"
  },

  {
    "question": "What day will you never see again?",
    "answer": "Yesterday",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Today",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Tomorrow",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Lastweek"
  },

  {
    "question": "What is the center of gravity?",
    "answer": "V",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Center",
    "wrongAnswer2": "10",
    "wrongAnswer3": "20"
  },

  {
    "question": "Sometimes I’m a sphere, sometimes I’m a banana, and sometimes I’m not there at all. What am I?",
    "answer": "A moon",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A sphere",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A banana",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "Shorter than my four siblings, but easily the strongest. Who am I?",
    "answer": "A thumb",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Zacchaeus",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Me",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "I’m so simple I only point, yet I guide people all over the world. What am I?",
    "answer": "A compass",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A clock",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A map",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A protractor"
  },

  {
    "question": "What can you catch but not throw?",
    "answer": "an illness",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A stone",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Money",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A ball"
  },

  {
    "question": "What runs around the yard without moving?",
    "answer": "A fence",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A rope",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A camera",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Nothing"
  },

  {
    "question": "What has teeth but can’t bite?",
    "answer": "A comb",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A gear",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A zipper",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A dog"
  },

  {
    "question": "Look in my face and I am someone, look in my back I am no one. What am I?",
    "answer": "A mirror",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A river",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A ghost",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A human"
  },

  {
    "question": "What 11-letter word does everyone pronounce incorrectly?",
    "answer": "Incorrectly",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Abstersives",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Adoptianist",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Antiquaries"
  },

  {
    "question": "What can split itself before splitting something else?",
    "answer": "Lightening",
    "wrongAnswer1": "An axe",
    "wrongAnswer2": "A volcano",
    "wrongAnswer3": "No answer"
  },

  {
    "question": "Right now everyone in the world, no matter where they are, is doing the exactly same thing. What is it?",
    "answer": "Getting older",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Making money",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Reading",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Walking"
  },

  {
    "question": "What goes up and down but doesn’t move?",
    "answer1": "Staircase",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Rain",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Clock",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A oscillating ball"
  },

  {
    "question": "What is placed on the table, cut and passed but never eaten?",
    "answer": "Game cards",
    "wrongAnswer1": "SPoilt cake",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Poisoned cheese",
    "wrongAnswer3": "Stale pizza"
  },

  {
    "question": "What is black when it’s clean and white when it’s dirty?",
    "answer": "A blackboard",
    "wrongAnswer1": "A black shirt",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Nothing",
    "wrongAnswer3": "A white shirt"
  },

  {
    "question": "What is made of wood but can’t be sawed?",
    "answer": "Sawdust",
    "wrongAnswer1": "Table",
    "wrongAnswer2": "Chair",
    "wrongAnswer3": "cupboard"
  }
]